<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research Staffs on NTU IoT Sensing Group</title>
    <link>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research Staffs on NTU IoT Sensing Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Duc Van Le</title>
      <link>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/duc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/duc/</guid>
      <description>Position: Research Fellow Contact: vdle@ntu.edu.sg Bio: Duc Van Le is research fellow at the HP-NTU Digital Manufacturing Corporate Lab, Nanyang Technological University (NTU), Singapore. He obtained his B.Eng. degree in electronics and telecommunications engineering from the Le Quy Don Technical University, Vietnam, and PhD degree in computer engineering from the University of Ulsan, South Korea, in 2011 and 2016, respectively. Before joining NTU, he worked as a research fellow at Department of Computer Science, National University of Singapore (NUS) from 2016 to 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuting Wu</title>
      <link>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/yuting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/yuting/</guid>
      <description> Position: Research Associate
Contact: yuting.wu@ntu.edu.sg
Bio: Yuting Wu received M.Sc. (2020) in Electrical and Electronic Engineering from Nanyang Technological University, Singapore, and his B.Eng degree in Automation from North-eastern University, China (2019). Previously, he was a Research Associate (2020-2021) at the Centre for System Intelligence and Efficiency, NTU, researching Reinforcement learning applications. Currently, He works as Research Associate on the SCALE project under Prof. Tan Rui.
Research projects:
Acoustic and imagery sensing </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhuoran Chen</title>
      <link>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/zhuoran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rrwang1.github.io/posts/members/staff/zhuoran/</guid>
      <description> Position: Project Officer
Contact: chen1192@e.ntu.edu.sg
Bio: Zhuoran Chen is a Project Officer at HP-NTU Digital Manufacturing Corporate Lab. He received his bachelor’s degree in computer engineering from Nanyang Technological University, Singapore, in 2021. His current research directions are 3D sensing and hardware acceleration in mobile computing.
Research projects:
Acoustic and imagery sensing </description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
