<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2. Publications on NTU IoT Research Group</title>
    <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2. Publications on NTU IoT Research Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Conference and workshop papers</title>
      <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Orientation-Aware 3D SLAM in Alternating Magnetic Field from Powerlines.. Rongrong Wang, Rui Tan, Zhenyu Yan, Chris Xiaoxuan Lu. Proceedings of the ACM on Interactive, Mobile, Wearable and Ubiquitous Technologies (IMWUT). The ACM International Joint Conference on Pervasive and Ubiquitous Computing (Ubicomp), October 5-9, 2024, Melbourne, Australia.
PDF
Susceptibility of Autonomous Driving Agents to Learning-Based Action-Space Attacks. Yuting Wu, Pengfei Zhou, Xin Lou, Rui Tan, Zbigniew Kalbarczyk, Ravishankar K. Iyer. The 9th International Workshop on Safety and Security Intelligent Vehicle (SSIV) with DSN&#39;23, June 27, 2023, Porto, Portugal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal papers</title>
      <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/journal/</guid>
      <description>Design, Deployment, and Evaluation of an Industrial AIoT System for Quality Control at HP Factories. Duc Van Le, Joy Qiping Yang; Siyuan Zhou; Daren Ho; Rui Tan. ACM Transactions on Sensor Networks (TOSN). In press. Preprint
Indoor Smartphone SLAM with Acoustic Echoes. Wenjie Luo, Qun Song, Zhenyu Yan, Rui Tan, Guosheng Lin. IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing (TMC). In press. Preprint
NNFacet: Splitting Neural Network for Concurrent Smart Sensors. Jiale Chen, Duc Van Le, Rui Tan, Daren Ho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thesis</title>
      <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/thesis/</guid>
      <description> **Exploiting Sensor and Process Characteristics to Tackle Label Scarcity in AIoT Sensing.**Wenjie LuoPDF **Exploiting Induced Skin Electric Potential for Body-Area IoT System Functions.**Zhenyu YanPDF **Exploiting LoRaWAN for Efficient and Resilient IoT Networks.**Chaojie GuPDF **Lightweight Privacy-Preserving Deep Learning and Inference in IoT.**Linshang JiangPDF **Improving Security of Autonomous Cyber-Physical Systems against Adversarial Examples.**Qun SongPDF </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book chapters</title>
      <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/book/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence of Things for Industrial Visual Sensing Systems in HP&amp;rsquo;s Factories.
Duc Van Le, Siyuan Zhou, Joy Qiping Yang, Jiale Chen, Daren Ho, Rui Tan. Digital Manufacturing, Vol. 2. Elsevier.
Lightweight Privacy-Preserving Machine Learning and Inference. Linshan Jiang and Rui Tan.
Intelligent IoT for the Digital World (Eds. Yang Yang, Xu Chen, Rui Tan, Yong Xiao). Wiley. In production.
Time Synchronization Management for Wide-Area Applications. Zhenyu Yan, Yang Li, and Rui Tan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical report</title>
      <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/report/</guid>
      <description> Tropical Data Centre Proof-of-Concept. Duc Van Le, Yingbo Liu; Rongrong Wang; Rui Tan. Technical Report, Nanyang Technological University, 2019. PDF </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard</title>
      <link>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/standard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntuiot.xyz/posts/papers/standard/</guid>
      <description> Deployment and Operation of Data Centre IT Equipment under Tropical Climate, Singapore Standard 697:2023 Link </description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
